Seduction. Betrayal. Murder. What are best friends for?
Breaking the Girls is a crime, thriller film directed by Jamie Babbit.
A naive college student loses a scholarship at the hands of a classmate and makes
a pact with a mysterious friend to kill off each other's enemies.
Sara Ryan, played by Agnes Bruckner.
Alex Layton, played by Madeline Zima.
Eric, played by Shawn Ashmore.
Brooke Potter, played by Shanna Collins.
Nina Layton, played by Kate Levering.
David Layton, played by John Stockwell.
Breaking the Girls is a 2012 American crime thriller film directed by
Jamie Babbit and starring Agnes Bruckner and Madeline Zima.
The tone is intense.